Thank you. Thank you, you may be seated.
Thank you Lord!
Emmanuel
God with us!
Hallelujah!
I know that you are blessed today.
Glory be to God Almighty!
This is the opportunity to ask the questions that people always ask me.
Anytime people meet me they will say
"How do I know what my calling from God is?"
Say to your neighbor, "how do I know what my calling if God is?"
That is the question.
But whatever you do through God the is your calling.
How can we do things through God?
When God speaks to us through his word, by His Spirit.
How do I know what my calling from God is?
Are you a carpenter?
Whatever he accepts you to do through Him, that is your calling.
People will say, what is my calling? Why did this happen to me?
Why am I not prospering?
Whenever you are dong something through God,
God will continue to speak strength and courage through your trials, take notice of that.
If God permits your to carry this through Him
I am carrying it through Him.
He will continue to speak strength and courage through my trials.
My trial could be this. It could be that.
Could be that.
Hallelujah!
The title is of this message is: "Call of God."
Say, "Call of God."
I can't hear you.
Congregation: Call of God
Congregation: Call of God.
Lets take a look at Psalm 119:105
Psalm 119:105
Read and follow me, "Your word is a lamp to my feet and a light to my path."
Wow!
Listen to that, it said...
Psalm 119:105 "Your word is a lamp to my feet and a light to my path."
So, that answered your question. What is my calling?
Am I really a lawyer?
If I am called as a lawyer, why is this happening to me?
Title of Message: "Call of God."
Am, I really a medical doctor?
If I am really a medical doctor, if this is my calling;
why is this happening to me?
Title of Message: "Call of God."
This has answered your question.
If His word is a lamp to your feet and a light to your path,
It means the first step in knowing your calling
is to get to know God better
by reading his word.
As God communicates to you through his word, by His Spirit,
you will know what He wants you to do and where He wants you to go.
He cannot interact you with.
He cannot act with you,
and you cannot hear from Him without His word.
Let's go to the book of Roman 12:2
Romans 12:2 It says, " Do not conform to this world, but be transformed
but be transformed by the renewing of your mind.
Romans 12:2 that you may prove what is that good and
and acceptable and perfect will of God."
When you let God transform you by the power of the Holy Spirit,
He will literally begin to show you the way...
He will literally begin to show you the way.
Then you can know,
where He wants you to go.
How He wants you to do this.
How He wants you to do that.
Many of us we don't allow God to transform us.
Not only must you become a pastor by HIs word, but by His Spirit.
HIs Word refreshes our mind and HIs Spirit renews our strength
He is waiting for you at the point of His Spirit.
You can go anywhere to learn his word.
You can choose to go to school, you can go to anywhere with no more problem
you can learn it. You can be very very thorough
But when it comes to His Spirit, He gives it.
You must be ready to be reformed.
You must abide by His principles.
You can learn his word.
Say "God is this. God is that."
God is Savior. God is this.
You can preach the word from Genesis to Revelation.
You have thorough knowledge of God, that does not make your His child.
Can you see where our problem is now?
That I standing here telling you that God is this. Jesus is this. Jesus is that.
It's just not enough to say that this is a man of God;
because anybody can stand here to preach it
whereas he's not
the one.
Not only must you have God's word in order to be born again,
you must have God's spirit.
Why?
Because God's word is the tool in the hands of the Holy Spirit.
Tell your neighbor, "God's word is the tool in the hands of the Holy Spirit."
If God's word is not in the hands of the Holy Spirit,
whatever you are saying, you are saying to yourself.
You are speaking of yourself and not of God.
God's word is the tool in the hands of the Holy Spirit
to nurture us and furnish us with everything that we need to succeed on earth.
Are you with me?
If God's word is not in the hands of the Holy Spirit,
whatever you are saying, you are speaking to yourself.
"Be healed!" You are wasting your time.
"Be delivered!" You are wasting your time.
"Be saved!" You are wasting your time.
You are prophesying that it will rain tomorrow. It will not rain!
Read it (the bible), it is food for your soul.
Read it, it is a guide for your feet.
Read it! It has a purifying power.
Read it! It has a coverting power.
It is enduring. Read it!
It rejoices the heart. Read it!
Read it!
To keep you from sin and error. Read it!
Read it! It is so profitable.
Like I have said,
"It is the tool in the hands of the Holy Ghost.
If it's not in the hands of the Holy Ghost, what ever you are saying,
you are talking of yourself.
That is why you see people saying "In the name of Jesus! In the name of Jesus!"
Sometime you see people people praying and praying.
Shaking, shaking, shaking, shaking.
Praying, praying.Jumping, jumping
At the end of the day it result into a headache.
Nothing will come out of it.
Many are getting frustrated fasting and praying,
and they begin to date and time they became a christian.
Many will read bible and place it on their chest, when they want to sleep.
That is where satan will come to flock them.
Even sometime satan will carry the bible from their chest and place it down
and begin to flock them, and say this bible, "where did you get it?"
There is a bible. There is a holy bible.
Anybody can buy a Bible; not everyone has access to a Holy Bible.
The bible is for sale, but the Holy Bible is not.
You can find a Bible in the library, but the Holy Bible is not in the library.
It's in your heart.
Many authors of this Bible that you have today
they are not christians. They are philosophers.
They wrote this bible for the sake of getting money out of it.
They are not christians, they don't believe what they have.
They are historical.
When you are carrying it, if it's not in the hands of the Holy Spirit,
you are just carrying a book.
When you talk, if it's not in the mouth of the Holy Ghost,
you are talking to yourself.
When you preach it, if that is not from the Holy Ghost,
you are just telling them history.
History is all about events, if it's not from the Holy Ghost.
Talk scripture in every conversation.
If you want to make a call, say "hello, hello?" "Oh, hello sir!"
"You are blessed!"
"With God all things are possible!"
You say, "thank you sir!"
Yes, "where are you going this morning?"
Carry God along. Talk scripture!
Your may be on the phone or in a business transaction, talk scripture.
Use the word of God to answer someone.
Tell your neighbor , "Use the word of God!"
Congregation: Use the word of God to answer someone.
The word of God becomes your data base for your personal opinion.
Title of Message: "Call of God."
But I want tell you, the questions you always ask, I believe a few of them have been answered.
That, "how do I know what my calling from God is?"
Congregation: "How do I know what my calling from God is?"
Again,"how do I know what my calling from God is?"
Congregation: how do I know what my calling from God is?
Look!
When I know your weakness, I will be able to help you and also trust you.
We can get on with this continuing.
You are because I am;
I am because you are.
I know you love to hahahah (laugh)
The reason why I am and you are is to help you and for you to help me.
When I know that you laugh anyhow, I know that is my own assignment to help you.
That will not cause our conflict. We will never fight because you laugh anyhow;
because I know your weakness, I will be thinking about how I can help you
get rid of that.
Look at what happened to Apostle Paul.
When your weakness is the midst of now drawing your close to God
to pray the more and fast more; it's no more a weakness. It is a blessing.
That is the thing in which the Bible is talking about.
The problem we have today is that you believe there is time to pray, fast, and say amen!
That is why satan gets your just like that.
Your alter is in your heart.
When you say you will wait to get to a place before you pray, before you get there, satan will get you.
They know you have a place to pray.
Nooooo!
When you move, you need to pray in you heart.
You heart, it is your alter.
Anytime there is an encounter either by thought or in your heart, you should immediately begin to blow him;
while you are standing, walking, and anywhere you are
begin to confess. Begin to say "you have come again?"
You don't know I am a child of God? I will deal with you!
I will finish you! Begin to talk again! Talk as if you are talking to a person.
See satan as a person.
The reason why satan wants you to talk his language
is to overthrow your position.
He wants you to overthrow your position. The position you occupy before God.
He wants to overthrow it.
That is the reason that he wants you to talk his language.
To think like him.
Once that thought is drawing you more and more into the midst of God, it is no longer satan's thought.
He is in the midst of strengthening your desire.
If you are where God wants you to be, even though you walk through
the valley of the shadow of death, you will fear no evil;
because you are where God wants you to be.
It is when we are not where God wants us to be, fear comes,
trouble comes.
But if you are where God want you to be,
the Lord will continue to speak strength and courage though your trials.
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip that you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, service, and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel Tv. Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.